Guide to the Garden Club of Allegheny County Records, 1913-2012 AIS.2006.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 2012-2013 Additions, 1934-2012; VIII.
  - Carrie T. Watson Proposal for Membership Correspondence (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Carrie T. Watson Photographs (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Carrie T. Watson Removable Media (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Flowers Show Photographs, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) Correspondence, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) Notes, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) Photographs of Artifacts, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) Photographs of Plants and Sculptures, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) Press Clippings, 1934 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Garden History and Design Committee, 2003-2006 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Horticulture Committee Reports and Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Insurance Documents, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - IRS and Tax-Exempt Documents, 1984-1985 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Living Treasure Award, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Living Treasure Award, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Member Lists [RESTRICTED], 1990-1992 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Member Lists [RESTRICTED], 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 2004-2006 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Nominating Committee Reports, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Official Website Design Documents (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Orientation History and Notes, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Before and After Photos (Box 82, Folder 45)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Design Specifications (Box 82, Folder 46)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Legal Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 82, Folder 47)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Legal Documents, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 48)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Legal Documents, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 49)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Notes (Box 82, Folder 50)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Project Media (VHS & CD's) (Box 82, Folder 51)
  - Phipps Conservatory Medicinal Garden Slides (Box 82, Folder 52)
  - Pizzazz Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 82, Folder 53)
  - Pizzazz Media (CD's), 2005-2008 (Box 82, Folder 54)
  - Pizzazz Photo Album, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 55)
  - Possession Obsession, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - President's Meeting, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Publications (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, Barkobils Farm (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Smithsonian Garden History, Application Hartwood County Park (aka Hartwood Acres) (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, La Petite Maison (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, La Petite Maison, Photographs (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, Newington (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Applications Media (CD's) (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, Spahr House Garden (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Smithsonian Garden History Application, Wilpen Hall (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Photographs (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Media (CD's and other) (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Zone V Awards Certificates (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Zone V Awards Requests and Proposals, 2000-2003 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Zone V Awards Requests and Proposals, 1997-1999 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Garden Art Exhibit (Carnegie Museum) 27 Photographs by R. P. Hay (14" x 11") (Box 84)